<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>NoOps Japan</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on NoOps Japan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/codeofconduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/codeofconduct/</guid>
      <description>NoOps Code of Conduct v1.0 日本語版 below
Introduction NoOps Community is dedicated to providing a harassment-free experience for participants at all of our events. NoOps Community events are working conferences intended for professional networking and collaboration. They exist to encourage the open exchange of ideas and expression and require an environment that recognizes the inherent worth of every person and group. While at NoOps Community events or related ancillary or social events, any participants, including speakers, attendees, volunteers, sponsors, exhibitors, booth staff and anyone else, should not engage in harassment in any form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/definition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/definition/</guid>
      <description>NoOps Definition v1.0 日本語版 below
NoOps stands for &amp;ldquo;No Uncomfortable Ops&amp;rdquo;.It is the combination of technology, architecture, and activities that enable the elimination of uncomfortable system operations. Designing container-based highly resilient systems, utilizing DevOps, automated monitoring/configuration and eliminating SRE Toil exemplify this approach.
Core capabilities, which are necessary to achieve NoOps, are high resiliency, observability, configurability, and security gurantees. Leveraging these capabilities allow us to realize the experience of self-healing, zero-downtime maintenance, adaptive scale, and safety everywhere.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>